<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">marine certificates</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <!-- Strings related to login -->
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="welcome">"Welcome!"</string>
    <string name="invalid_username">Not a valid username</string>
    <string name="invalid_password">Password must be >5 characters</string>
    <string name="login_failed">"Login failed"</string>
    <string name="search" />
    <string name="STCW_Discrip">"The maritime safety institutes offers training to officers and engineers working onboard all types of ships."</string>
    <string name="MarineSafety_Discrip">"international regulations in the maritime industry and its reflection on the management of shipping and offshore companies as well as personal working on-board ships and offshore installation."</string>
    <string name="Offshore_Discrip">"The maritime safety institute offers training and education for personnel working in the offshore industry onboard oil rigs and platforms in accordance with the IMO regulations and OPITO standards."</string>
    <string name="MarineSimulators_Discrip">"Marine simulators represent critical elements for the preventing of marine disasters and pollution, equipped with sophisticated facilities of high capabilities which are able to simulate numerous realistic situations and conditions sufficient for a wide variety of effective training and covering several applications and courses in a wide range of Maritime Education Training and port operations."</string>
    <string name="EnvironmentalProtection_Discrip">"The Crisis and Disaster Management Simulator is a complete, fully automated system used for training &amp; managing real-time emergency response dealing with a variety of natural and man-made crisis according to a pre-designed contingency plan."</string>
    <string name="GMDSS_Discrip">"The simulated communications equipment accurately replicate the GMDSS''s functions that meet the requirements of the International Convention on Standards of Training, Certification and Watch keeping for seafarers (STCW-1978) and its amendments that is set by the IMO."</string>
    <string name="NaturalGas_Petrochemicals_Discrip">"The Simulator introduces new training methods to supplement the traditional methods on board training. The liquid Cargo operations simulator provides real time simulation of the process Flow Control Systems used in storage and transfer of potentially hazardous bulk liquid from shore to ship and ship to shore. The Simulator allows a range of courses to be offered which are presently applicable to both ship and shore involved in handling of LNG, LPG, Crude oil, oil Products and Chemical Cargoes."</string>
    <string name="Meteorology_HydrographicSurvey_Discrip">"Meteorology, the science of atmospheric phenomena, has been an active area of science for hundreds of years. Furthermore, renewed considerable interest in meteorology has revived recently primarily because of the growing awareness of the risk of significant changes in the Earth’s weather and climate."</string>
    <string name="Diving_Discrip">"Diving is now considered one of the main activities and jobs in the offshore and inshore industries. Offshore industry is one of the most important economical sources around the world. Diving is now also considered a main branch in several activities, including, but not limited to, civil engineering works, harbour works, tourism, etc"</string>
    <string name="STCWCRT_Discrip">"Required Courses are : \n.PERSONAL SAFETY AND SCOCIAL RESPONSIBILITIES\n.Fire Prevention and Fire Fighting\n.Elementary First Aid\n.Proficiency of Security Awareness Training for Seafarers with Designated Security\n.Proficiency in Personal Survival Techniques and Search and Rescue ."</string>
    <string name="ChiefOfficer_Discrip">"Required Courses are : \n.Proficiency in survival craft and rescue boats other than fast rescue boats\n.Advanced Fire Prevention and Fire Fighting Course\n.PERSONAL SAFETY AND SCOCIAL RESPONSIBILITIES\n.Medical care Studies\n.Refreshment course (management level) Nautical Department\n.Proficiency of Security Awareness Training for Seafarers with Designated Security\n.Advanced personal survival and search and rescue ."</string>
    <string name="ThirdOfficer_Discrip">"Required Courses are : \n.Proficiency in survival craft and rescue boats other than fast rescue boats\n.Advanced Fire Prevention and Fire Fighting Course\n.PERSONAL SAFETY AND SCOCIAL RESPONSIBILITIES\n.Proficiency of Security Awareness Training for Seafarers with Designated Security\n.Medical First Aid\n.Proficiency in Personal Survival Techniques and Search and Rescue\n.Refreshment Course (Operational Level) Nautical Department."</string>
    <string name="ThirdEngineer_Discrip">"Required Courses are : \n.Proficiency in survival craft and rescue boats other than fast rescue boats\n.Advanced Fire Prevention and Fire Fighting Course\n.PERSONAL SAFETY AND SCOCIAL RESPONSIBILITIES\n.Proficiency of Security Awareness Training for Seafarers with Designated Security\n.Medical First Aid\n.Proficiency in Personal Survival Techniques and Search and Rescue\n.Refreshment Course (Operational Level) Nautical Department."</string>
    <string name="SecondEngineer_Discrip">"Required Courses are : \n.Proficiency in survival craft and rescue boats other than fast rescue boats\n.Advanced Fire Prevention and Fire Fighting Course\n.PERSONAL SAFETY AND SCOCIAL RESPONSIBILITIES\n.Proficiency of Security Awareness Training for Seafarers with Designated Security\n.Medical First Aid\n.Proficiency in Personal Survival Techniques and Search and Rescue\n.Refreshment Course (Operational Level) Nautical Department."</string>
    <string name="SecondOfficer_Discrip">"Required Courses are : \n.Proficiency in survival craft and rescue boats other than fast rescue boats\n.Advanced Fire Prevention and Fire Fighting Course\n.PERSONAL SAFETY AND SCOCIAL RESPONSIBILITIES\n.Proficiency of Security Awareness Training for Seafarers with Designated Security\n.Medical First Aid\n.Proficiency in Personal Survival Techniques and Search and Rescue\n.Refreshment Course (Operational Level) Nautical Department."</string>
    <string name="ChiefEngineer_Discrip">"Required Courses are : \n.Proficiency in survival craft and rescue boats other than fast rescue boats\n.Advanced Fire Prevention and Fire Fighting Course\n.PERSONAL SAFETY AND SCOCIAL RESPONSIBILITIES\n.Proficiency of Security Awareness Training for Seafarers with Designated Security Duties\n.Medical First Aid\n.Proficiency in Personal Survival Techniques and Search and Rescue\n.( Management Level ) Refreshment Course Engineering Department."</string>

</resources>